Guide to the Beer Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Mooney, R. J., 1907-1908, 1910
Moore, John Bassett 1913, 1915
Morey, John J. (Cuba) 1913-1915
Moriarty, S. F. (American Rapid Boat Company) 1905-1906
Mosca, Tommaso 1914
Mullins, W. H. (American Rapid Boat Company) 1905-1906, 1908
Neilson, Charles (The Safety Car Heating and Lighting Company, Dominican Republic) 1913-1914
Osborne, Harrison (lemons) 1910-1916
Osterheld, Theodore W. (lemons) 1912-1913
Page, Thomas Nelson 1914
Palmer, Charles Day 1884, 1895-1896, 1911
Palmer, Frederick L. 1882, 1890
Pepperman, W. Leon (Ass't. Chief, Isthmian Canal Affairs) 1905-1907
Perkins, George W., 1899, 1902-1906, 1908-1909, 1911, 1914-1915
Pickford, A. J. 1913
Platt, Thomas Collier 1905, 1907
Reid, John W. 1900-1905
Richards, William M. (Fidelity and Casualty Company of New. York) 1889-1891
Roosevelt, Theodore 1903
Root, Elihu 1911
Rosen, Baron 1910-1912, 1915-1916
Sanderson, George A. 1915-1916
Schlobohm, William A. (lemons) 1914-1916
Simpson, SS (Panama Canal) 1912-1913, 1916
Smith, Joseph P. 1896-1897
Smoot, Reed 1904, 1906-1907, 1909-1911
Stedman, Emory A. (Wells Fargo) 1903, 1905-1913, 1915-1916
Stewart, Alonzo Hopkins 1909-1911, 1913-1915
Stillwell, A. E. 1898
Stubbs, David T. 1890, 1893, 1896-1897
Styer, Henry D. 1882-1883, 1885, 1887, 1890-1891, 1893-1894,1899, 1909, 1911
Sullivan James M. (Dominican Republic) 1913-1915
Symington, T. H. (munitions) 1915
Talbott, W. M. (Cuba) 1912
Thompson, David E. (Mexico) 1904-1906, 1908-1910
Tinker, Jackson (Cuba) 1913
Torriente, Cosme de la (Cuba) 1910-1916
Treat, Charles H. (Manila Navigation Company) 1901-1903,1905-1909
Underwood, Oscar W. 1911-1916
Valentine, John J. (Wells Fargo) 1889,1895, 1900
Warfield, Edwin (Fidelity and Deposit Company of Maryland) 1896, [1909]
Wheeler, John N. 1912-1913
Whiting, Julius, Jr. 1896-1900, 1902, 1905, 1907-1910, 1913-1914, 1916
Wills, A. W. (munitions) 1915-1916
Wilson, Huntington 1910
Yaselli, Emilio (lemons) 1912-1916
Yerkes, John W. 1901,1904
Young, Sir William Lawrence (Cuba) 1912-1915
Lemons./See: G. Dominici, George E. Gilliland, Samuel M. Jarvis, Joseph N. LoMedico, Cameron Mackenzie, John H. Mason, Bernardo Mercandante, Harrison Osborne, Theodore W. Osterheld, William A. Schlobohm, Oscar W. Underwood, Emilio Yaselli
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Business; Chickamauga, Battle of, Ga., 1863; Decoration and ornament; Embroidery; Emigration and immigration; Families; Great Fire, Chicago, Ill., 1871; Law; Literature -- History and criticism; Medicine -- United States; Pioneers -- Michigan; Ranch life; Religion; Religious education; Shipping; Students; Tariff on farm produce; Textile fabrics; Women; World War, 1914-1918 -- Personal narratives, American; World War, 1914-1918; Asia; Bucyrus (Ohio); Canada; Cuba -- Foreign economic relations -- United States; Dominican Republic -- Foreign economic relations -- United States; Europe -- Description and travel; Great Britain; Hungary -- History -- 1918-1945; Italy -- Foreign economic relations -- United States; Latin America; Middle East; Middle West; Philippines -- Description and travel; United States -- Foreign economic relations -- Cuba; United States -- Foreign economic relations -- Dominican Republic; United States -- Foreign economic relations -- Italy; United States -- Foreign relations; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865; United States -- Politics and government; United States -- Social life and customs -- 1865-1918; West (U.S.); Diaries; Photoprints; Authors; Businessmen; Clergy; Lobbyists; Museum curators; Allen, Frederick Lewis, 1890-1954; Babbitt, Edwin Burr, 1862-1939; Baldwin, Linus Caleb, 1831-1910; Beer, Alice Baldwin, 1887-1981; Beer, Martha A. A.; Beer, R. (Richard Cameron), 1893-1959; Beer, Samuel Hutchinson, 1911-; Beer, Thomas, 1889-1940; Beer, William Collins, 1863-1916; Bellows, George, 1882-1925; Benton, Thomas Hart, 1889-1975; Bernstein, Aline, 1881-1955; Beveridge, Albert J. (Albert Jeremiah), 1862-1927; Boyd, Ernest Augustus, 1887-1946; Brooks, Van Wyck, 1886-1963; Cabell, James Branch, 1879-1958; Canby, Henry Seidel, 1878-1961; Cheney, Benjamin Pierce, 1815-1895; Conrad, Joseph, 1857-1924; Cortelyou, George B. (George Bruce), 1862-1940; Crane, Stephen, 1871-1900; Dawes, Charles Gates, 1865-1951; Depew, Chauncey M. (Chauncey Mitchell), 1834-1928; Fisher, Harold H. (Harold Henry), 1890-1975; Foraker, Joseph Benson, 1846-1917; Garland, Hamlin, 1860-1940; Garnett, Edward, 1868-1937; Hanna, Marcus Alonzo, 1837-1904; Housum, Robert, 1886-1986; Knopf, Alfred A., 1892-1984; Knopf, Blanche W., 1894-1966; Lombardi, Cornelius Ennis, 1888-1956; McAdoo, W. G. (William Gibbs), 1863-1941; McKinley, William, 1843-1901; Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1880-1956; Millard, Joseph Hopkins, 1836-1922; Minnigerode, Meade, 1887-1967; Morley, Christopher, 1890-1957; Mumford, Lewis, 1895-1990; Norris, Charles G. (Charles Gilman), 1881-1945; Norris, Kathleen Thompson, 1880-1966; Ober, Harold, 1881-1959; Page, Thomas Nelson, 1853-1922; Pemberton, Brock, 1885-1950; Perkins, George W. (George Walbridge), 1862-1920; Phelps, William Lyon, 1865-1943; Pigott, William Trigg, 1861-1944; Rambo, James Irving, 1923-; Reynolds, Paul Revere, 1864-1944; Riggs, T. Lawrason (Thomas Lawrason), 1888-1943; Robinson, Henry Augustus, Sir, 1857-1927; Smoot, Reed, 1862-1941; Street, Julian, 1870-1947; Styer, Henry Delp, 1862-1944; Swinnerton, Frank, 1884-1982; Tarkington, Booth, 1869-1946; Thompson, David E. (David Eugene), 1854-1942; Tilghman, James D.; Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1876-1963; Toohey, John Peter, 1880-1946; Tuttle, H. E. (Henry Emerson), 1890-1946; Underwood, Oscar W. (Oscar Wilder), 1862-1929; Walpole, Hugh, 1884-1941; William, Wayland Wells, 1888-1945; Woolley, Monty, 1888-1963; Beers family; Cooper-Hewitt Museum; J.P. Morgan & Co; Manila Navigation Company; New York Life Insurance Company; United States Military Academy; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1911; Yale University -- Students
- FAMILY: GENERAL, 1851-1969; Series I; 22.7' (55 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by writer. Letters by a particular writer have been arranged chronologically, except where there is a large group of letters to another individual. In such a case, the group has been placed after the general chronological Sequence. For example, after Alice (Boyle) Baldwin's letters to the family in general, there is a new sequence, "To Linus Caleb Baldwin." Non-family correspondence of those individuals who are not represented in separate series, is filed immediately following their family correspondence. Miscellaneous family letters and correspondence of others are filed at the end of the section.
  Sermons of Reverend Thomas Beer is arranged chronologically.
  Financial Files is arranged alphabetically by the names of family members, with the exception of the first section: Family Real Estate and Property.
  Personal Files is arranged alphabetically by the names of family members.
  Photographs is arranged alphabetically by subject, with group pictures of family and friends at the end of the section.
  Genealogy and Biography is arranged alphabetically by family name.
  - Correspondence
    - Baldwin, Alice (Boyle), 1889-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    - Baldwin, Alice (Boyle) to Linus Caleb Baldwin, 1861-1874 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Baldwin, Alice (Boyle). Correspondence with non-family members, 1859-1874 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Baldwin, Benjamin Pitney, Sr., 1856-1881 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      General note
      See also: box 1, folder 11
    - Baldwin, Benjamin Pitney, Jr., 1851-1918, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Baldwin, Caleb, 1871-1876 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Baldwin, Helen M.
      See: box 25, folder 307
    - Baldwin, Henry Boyd and Barbara (Pow)., 1856-1880 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Baldwin, James Pauley, 1856-1857 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Baldwin, Linus Caleb, 1862-1901 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
    - Baldwin, Linus Caleb, 1902-1910, undated (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
    - Baldwin, Linus Caleb to Alice (Boyle) Baldwin, 1861-1862, 1878-1899, undated (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
    - Baldwin, Linus Caleb to Alice Baldwin, Richard Cameron, and Thomas Beer, 1895-1909, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Baldwin, Nehemia Scott and Melissa (Pierce)., 1869-1879 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      See also: box 1, folder 7
    - Baldwin, Robert Caleb, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      See also: boxes 56-84, folders 1-358
    - Baldwin, Robert Caleb, 1899-1905 (Box 2, Folder 21-26)
    - Correspondence about Robert Caleb, Baldwin, 1937-1946 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Baldwin Family, 1856-1937 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin, 1891-1911 (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin, 1930-1940, 1945-1969 (Box 3, Folder 31-33)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to Doris Riker Beer, 1944, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer, 1901-1937 (Box 3, Folder 35-40)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer and William Collins Beer, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to Richard Cameron and Thomas Beer, 1911-1930 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to Richard Cameron Beer, 1938-1959 (Box 4, Folder 44-46)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to Thomas Beer, 1906-1922, 1937-1940 (Box 4, Folder 47-49)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to William Collins Beer, 1891-1911 (Box 4, Folder 50-55)
    - Beer, Alice Baldwin to William Collins Beer, 1912-1914 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Beer, Ashbel Greene, 1872-1882 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Beer, Dorcas Grizzel ("Dot"), 1882-1889 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Beer, Dorcas Grizzel, 1890-1916, 1929-1951, undated (Box 5, Folder 59-61)
    - Beer, Dorcas Grizzel to Mary Elizabeth (Beer) Lothian, 1893-1912 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Beer, Dorcas Grizzel. Correspondence with non-family members, 1889-1933 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Beer, Dorcas Katherine.
      See: box 24, folders 295-297
    - Beer, Doris Riker to Alice Baldwin Beer, 1937-1953, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 64-66)
    - Beer, James D., 1881-1910 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Beer, Jeane L. (Mrs. James D.), 1888-1914 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Beer, Katherine Jeannette ("Kit"), 1882-1896 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Beer, Katherine Jeannette, 1897-1946, undated (Box 6, Folder 70-71)
    - Beer, Katherine Jeannette. Correspondence with non-family members, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Beer, Margaret Cameron, 1908-1915, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Beer, Margaret Cameron Lee (Mrs. Thomas), 1875-1877, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Beer, Margaret Mary and Jeane, 1904-1940 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin), 1887-1915, 1929-1940 (Box 6, Folder 76-78)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to Alice (Boyle) and Linus Caleb Baldwin, 1872-1881 (Box 6, Folder 79-80)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to Linus Caleb Baldwin, 1907-1910 (Box 6, Folder 81-82)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to Alice Baldwin Beer, 1898-1903 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to Alice Baldwin Beer, 1906-1910 (Box 7, Folder 84-90)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to Alice Baldwin Beer, 1913-1919 (Box 7, Folder 91-92)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to Alice Baldwin Beer, 1929-1940 (Box 7, Folder 93-94)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to Richard Cameron Beer., 1903-1913 (Box 7, Folder 95)
      See also: MAABB to Thomas Beer
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to Richard Cameron Beer, 1914, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 96-97)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to Thomas Beer, 1893-1914, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 98-101)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to William Collins Beer, 1884 April-December (Box 8, Folder 102-105)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to William Collins Beer, 1885-1886, 1896-1911 (Box 9, Folder 106-114)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin) to William Collins Beer, August 1911-1914 (Box 10, Folder 115-116)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin). Correspondence with non-family members, 1885-1941, undated (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin): birthday congratulations, 1917-1939, undated (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Beer, Martha A. A. (Baldwin): letters of condolence on her death., 1940 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Beer, Mary Elizabeth ("Puss")
      See: box 46, folder 512
    - Beer, Mary Goodrich (Fitch), 1909-1921, undated (Box 10, Folder 120-122)
    - Beer, Mary G. F., 1920-1937, 1940-1949 (Box 10, Folder 123-124)
    - Beer, Mary G. F., 1950-1959 (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Beer, Mary G. F. Correspondence with non-family members, 1933-1938, undated (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Beer, Paul, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Beer, R. C. and Robert, 1869-1912 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron, 1895-1914 (Box 11, Folder 129-132)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron and Elizabeth (Thompson), 1915-1916 (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron, 1917-1924 (Box 11, Folder 134-139)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron, 1937-1940, 1953-1959, undated (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron to Alice Baldwin Beer, 1922-1933, 1137-1948 (Box 12, Folder 142-151)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron to Alice Baldwin Beer, 1949-1959 (Box 13, Folder 152-160)
    - Beer, Richard Cameron: letters of condolence on his death, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 161)
    - Beer, Richard Quince.
      See: box 23, folder 275
    - Beer, Robert Lea, 1881-1905, 1907-1909 (Box 13, Folder 162-163)
    - Beer, Robert Lea, 1910-1912, undated (Box 14, Folder 164)
    - Beer, Robert Lea to Mary Elizabeth (Beer) Lothian, 1893-1912 (Box 14, Folder 165)
    - Beer, Samuel H., 1950-1966 (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Beer, Tabitha Mary (Dinsmore), 1869-1913, undated (Box 14, Folder 167-170)
    - Beer, Tabitha Mary (Dinsmore). Correspondence with non-family members, Circa 1850, 1851-1852 (Box 14, Folder 171-172)
    - Beer, Tabitha Mary (Dinsmore). Correspondence with non-family members, 1853-1872, 1881-1915 (Box 14, Folder 173-176)
    - Beer, Rev. Thomas, 1863-1886, undated (Box 14, Folder 177)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to his children (jointly addressed), 1871-1907 (Box 14, Folder 178)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to his children, 1908-1910, undated (Box 15, Folder 179-181)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to Alice Baldwin, Richard Cameron and Thomas Beer, 1892-1908, undated (Box 15, Folder 182)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to Dorcas Grizzel Beer, 1873-1904, undated (Box 15, Folder 183-184)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to Katherine Jeannette Beer, 1873-1910, undated (Box 15, Folder 185)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to Robert Lee Beer, 1874-1910, undated (Box 15, Folder 186)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to Tabitha Mary (Dinsmore) Beer, 1873 (Box 15, Folder 187)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to Tabitha Mary (Dinsmore) Beer, 1904-1909, undated (Box 15, Folder 188-189)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to William Collins Beer, 1880-1908 (Box 15, Folder 190-193)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to Mary Elizabeth (Beer) Lothian, 1880-1909, undated (Box 16, Folder 194-202)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas to "Dear Brother", 1899-1909 (Box 16, Folder 203)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas and Tabitha Mary (Dinsmore): 50th wedding anniversary greetings, 1906 (Box 16, Folder 204)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas: letters on a eulogy after his death, August-December 1910 (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - Beer, Judge Thomas. Correspondence with non-family members, 1896-1910 (Box 17, Folder 206)
    - Beer, Thomas (son of James D.), 1910, 1914, 1915, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 207)
    - Beer, Thomas (son of William Collins), 1895-1901 (Box 17, Folder 208)
    - Beer, Thomas, 1902-1914 (Box 17, Folder 209-217)
    - Beer, Thomas, 1916-1917 (Box 18, Folder 218-219)
    - Beer, Thomas (in the United States), 1918 (Box 18, Folder 220)
    - Beer, Thomas (in England), 1918 (Box 18, Folder 221)
    - Beer, Thomas (in France), 1918 (Box 18, Folder 222)
    - Beer, Thomas, 1919-1939, undated (Box 18, Folder 223-225)
    - Beer, Thomas Cameron, 1871-1933, undated (Box 18, Folder 226)
    - Beer, Thomas Cameron to Alice Baldwin, Richard Cameron and Thomas Beer, 1891-1899 (Box 18, Folder 227)
    - Beer, Thomas Cameron to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) and William Collins Beer, 1887-1915, undated (Box 18, Folder 228)
    - Beer, William Collins, 1874-1882, 1886-1898 (Box 18, Folder 229-231)
    - Beer, William Collins, 1900-1916, undated (Box 19, Folder 232-233)
    - Beer, William Collins to Alice Baldwin Beer, 1900-1914 (Box 19, Folder 234-237)
    - Beer, William Collins to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer, 1883-1884 (Box 19, Folder 238-240)
    - Beer, William Collins to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer, July-December 1884-1895 (Box 20, Folder 241-248)
    - Beer, William Collins to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer, 1896- 1900, 1901 July-1904 (Box 21, Folder 249-256)
    - Beer, William Collins to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer, 1905-1916, undated (Box 22, Folder 257-260)
    - Beer, William Collins to Thomas Beer, 1891-1916 (Box 22, Folder 261-265)
    - Beer, William N. to Judge Thomas Beer., 1862-1865, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 266)
      See also: Samuel N. Beer
    - Beer Family, 1882-1937, undated (Box 22, Folder 266)
    - Boyle, Ann (Miller), 1852-[1903?], undated (Box 22, Folder 268)
    - Boyle, James, 1861-1875 (Box 23, Folder 269)
    - Boyle, Lucius Robert, 1858-1890 (Box 23, Folder 270)
    - Boyle, Robert Sturgeon, 1861-1875 (Box 23, Folder 271)
    - Boyle, Walter Vance, 1872 (Box 23, Folder 272)
    - Boyle Family, 1861-1862, undated (Box 23, Folder 273)
    - Collins Family, 1856-1888, undated (Box 23, Folder 274)
    - Coss, Mabel (Beer) and John, 1940, 1951, undated (Box 23, Folder 275)
    - DePue, Charles Caleb and William Baldwin, 1877-1913 (Box 23, Folder 276)
    - DePue, Lois R. (Baldwin) and Marshall Scott, 1856-1894 (Box 23, Folder 277)
    - Dinsmore, Andrew A., 1874-1918
    - Dinsmore, Mabel L. (Box 23, Folder 278)
      See: box 23, folder 283
    - Dinsmore, Rachel, 1874-1888 (Box 23, Folder 279)
    - Dinsmore Family, 1852-1940 (Box 23, Folder 280)
    - Duncan, Mary (Beer), 1873-1916 (Box 23, Folder 281)
    - Flower, Margaret (Coss), 1932-1940 (Box 23, Folder 282)
    - Hill, Mabel (Dinsmore) and James Hall, 1902-1960 (Box 23, Folder 283)
    - Lea, Mary (Beer) and Richard, 1887-1896 (Box 23, Folder 284)
    - Lothian, Isaac A. and Bella D., 1914-1916 (Box 23, Folder 285)
    - Lothian, Mary Elizabeth (Beer) ("Puss"), 1874-1902 (Box 24, Folder 286)
    - Lothian, Mary Elizabeth (Beer), 1903-1917, undated (Box 24, Folder 287)
    - Lothian, Mary Elizabeth (Beer).Correspondence with non-family members, 1873-1904 (Box 24, Folder 288)
    - Lothian, Mary Elizabeth (Beer).Correspondence with non-family members, 1907-1916, undated (Box 24, Folder 289)
    - Miller Family, 1860-1862 (Box 24, Folder 290)
    - Mitchell, David and Mattie, 1856, 1870 (Box 24, Folder 291)
    - Murdoch, Anna V., John, and Martha (Boyle), 1862-1936 (Box 24, Folder 292)
    - Officer, Margaret (Boyle) and Charles T., 1869-1940 (Box 24, Folder 293)
    - Pow, Alexander, Harriet C. (Baldwin) and Libbie, 1856-1880 (Box 24, Folder 294)
    - Reece, Dorcas Katherine (Beer), 1900-1914, 1932-1969 (Box 24, Folder 295-297)
    - Reece, Dorcas Katherine (Beer), Undated [probably circa 1930s] (Box 25, Folder 298)
    - Reece, Dorcas Katherine (Beer): undated letters to Bucyrus family, [ca. 1928?-1930s?], [ca. 1930s?] (Box 25, Folder 299-301)
    - Reece, Dorcas Katherine (Beer). Correspondence with non-family members, 1914-1936 (Box 25, Folder 302)
    - Reece, Sarah Nancy, 1933-1936, undated (Box 25, Folder 303)
    - Reed, Jennett E. and Joseph R., 1854-1886, undated (Box 25, Folder 304)
    - Rupp, Anna (Boyle), 1861-1924 (Box 25, Folder 305)
    - Scott, James D., 1853-1855 (Box 25, Folder 306)
    - Tyler, Helen M. (Baldwin), 1904-1907 (Box 25, Folder 307)
    - Tyler, Helen M. (Baldwin) to Alice Baldwin Beer, 1903-1910 (Box 25, Folder 308)
    - Tyler, Helen M. (Baldwin) to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer, 1898-1904 (Box 25, Folder 309)
    - Tyler, Helen M. (Baldwin) to Martha A. A. (Baldwin) Beer, 1905-1913 (Box 26, Folder 310)
    - Tyler, Helen M. (Baldwin) to Richard Cameron Beer, 1904-1910 (Box 26, Folder 311)
    - Tyler, Helen M. (Baldwin) to Thomas Beer, 1904-1909 (Box 26, Folder 312)
    - Tyler, James W., 1907-1947, undated (Box 26, Folder 313)
    - Tyler, John B. and Jane, 1942-1951 (Box 26, Folder 314)
    - Miscellaneous family letters, 1851-1888, undated (Box 26, Folder 315)
    - Correspondence of others, Circa 1850-1901 (Box 26, Folder 316)
  - Sermons of Reverend Thomas Beer
    - 1829-1830 (Box 26, Folder 317-319)
    - 1831-1832 (Box 27, Folder 320)
    - 1834, 1852, 1857, 1861, 1869 (Box 27, Folder 322)
    - undated (Box 27, Folder 323-326)
  - Financial Files
    - Family Real Estate and Property
      - Crestline, Ohio Property: correspondence, receipts, 1897-1940 (Box 28, Folder 327)
      - Siasconset Property: maps of property lots ca. 1880-1890. (Box 28, Folder 327)
        See also: box 33, folder 380
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence, receipts concerning purchase, 1906-1910 (Box 28, Folder 328)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence, bills and receipts re: taxes, 1905 (Box 28, Folder 329)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence with Clark, Vanderhoof and Little, 1927-1929 (Box 28, Folder 330)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence, bills and receipts concerning taxes and mortgage, 1931, 1937-1939 (Box 28, Folder 331)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence, bills and receipts for repairs, maintenance, utilities, 1938-1941 (Box 28, Folder 332)
      - Siasconset Property: insurancepolicies and statements, 1938-1941 (Box 28, Folder 333)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence, bills and receipts concerning taxes and mortgage, 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 334)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence concerning rental, 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 335-336)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence, bills, receipts re: rental, maintenance, taxes, 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 337-338)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence re: insurance, rental, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 339)
      - Siasconset Property: bills, receipts, insurance policies, notes, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 340)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence, bills, receipts, 1945-1946 (Box 29, Folder 341)
      - Siasconset Property: insurance: correspondence and policies, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 342)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence with attorneys, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 343)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence, bills, receipts, insurance, notes, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 344)
      - Siasconset Property: bills, receipts, insurance, notes, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 345)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 346-347)
      - Siasconset Property: correspondence re: sale of property, deeds, insurance, 1960-1964 (Box 29, Folder 348)
      - Yonkers Property: bills and receipts for expenses, insurance, 1902-1903 (Box 29, Folder 349)
      - Yonkers Property: tax records, 1903-1943 (Box 29, Folder 350)
      - Yonkers Property: correspondence, receipts re: purchase of additional property, 1911-1915 (Box 29, Folder 351)
      - Yonkers Property: bills and receipts for maintenance, 1916-1928 (Box 30, Folder 352)
      - Yonkers Property: insurance (1), 1914-1941 (Box 30, Folder 353)
      - Yonkers Property: insurance (2), 1914-1941 (Box 30, Folder 354)
      - Yonkers Property: correspondence, bills and receipts for maintenance (1), 1933-1940 (Box 30, Folder 355)
      - Yonkers Property: correspondence, bills and receipts for maintenance (2), 1933-1940 (Box 30, Folder 356)
      - Yonkers Property: correspondence, bills and receipts for maintenance and rental, 1940-1945 (Box 30, Folder 357-358)
      - Yonkers Property: bank correspondence, statements and receipts, 1938-1940 (Box 30, Folder 359)
      - Yonkers Property: bank correspondence, statements and receipts, 1941-1944 (Box 31, Folder 360-361)